You did say under the
chin, right, Polnareff?
What the hell?!
Remember me, you fool?
I'm the Anubistan you fought earlier!
Matt, what do I do now? Goodbye!
I'm gonna shave your jaw clean off!
Who the hell are you, really?
And what have you done with the barber?
Wait, could it possibly be that?
The sword is actually the stand?
Could it be controlling the barber?
So the guy at Khan Ombo wasn't
a real stand user? Hold on!
But in the end, it doesn't matter.
I'm still way out of your league, buddy.
What?
How are you so strong?
If you must know,
I took the liberty of learning
chariots' moves during our last fight.
I won't lose twice to the same adversary.
Do you understand me?
To you, in a fire,
I will face the love of my eyes.
I will face you again.
To you, in aаны, I will face
you again? To you, in a moment.
The end of the dark, the end of the dark,
A real sombra, the end of the dark, The
angel of the devil That's what I know of,
I will face you again
END OF THE WORLD
that's it you can do it yeah come on you
can't give up now you've almost got it
polnareff and jotaro they
should have returned by now
Polareff, what's going on?
The Barber's a stand user?
Stay back, Jotaro!
The sword is the stand!
Trust me,
it's too dangerous to try using Star
Platinum's bare fist against this blade!
The sword's sharp enough
to slice through them!
This Barber isn't the stand
user, he's just a puppet!
And that's not even the worst part!
The stand's even stronger
than it was before!
Bastard!
Whoa there!
Too much for you?
I suppose I should be grateful you've
shown me the limits of your defense.
Most kind of you.
Now then, let's see if you have what
it takes to survive my next attack.
Shall we, Polnareff? Time.
Polareff!
His powers keep increasing!
With every strike!
I can't keep parrying forever!
Sooner or later he's gonna get me!
Now!
Take this!
How in the...
In case you haven't realized the
obvious, I know all your moves.
It doesn't matter who my wielder is,
as long as I've done battle
with you at least once.
I never ever,
I'm not gonna win this without my rapier.
Oh, no!
Jotaro, help me out here!
Star Platinum.
Think that finished him off?
No.
That punch was shallow.
Even though it took just
about everything I had.
Shit.
This guy's strong.
It's been quite a while now since
we've seen a stand like this one.
It only relies on strength.
Not bad, Star Platinum.
The rumors of your speed were true.
But now that I've seen it,
I can easily defeat it.
Hey, Khan, what's wrong with you?
Stay back!
Your friend is being controlled.
If you don't want to get sliced to
ribbons, go back inside and hide!
We're in major trouble, Jotaro.
The more we fight this
stand, the faster it gets.
And its next attack will probably
be its fastest and strongest yet.
We have to be ready for whatever this
glorified butter knife throws at us!
Move, Polareff!
I'm the one it's really after!
Get out of there, Jotaro! Die!
What?
With his bare hands?
Amazing!
For him to take that great of a risk!
Now it's become abundantly clear.
The true source of Star Platinum's
strength isn't its speed or precision.
It's Jotaro's nerves of steel and
ability to make quick decisions.
Yes, now I know it.
For sure.
Is he dead?
Hold on a second, Jotaro.
He's just knocked out!
Whatever you do, don't touch that sword.
You snapped it in half, but the stand's
powers might still be lingering.
It controls anyone who
touches it while unsheathed.
Let's get the blade back inside
without touching the hilt.
Now what?
If someone draws it again, we're done for.
This damn thing has already
learned all of our abilities.
I don't think we're gonna
get any second chances.
Why not toss it into the river to
rust at the bottom of the Nile?
The Nile, huh?
That sounds like a great plan to me.
Hold it!
This is the police!
This is perfect timing.
This guy needs a hospital.
I have multiple reports of
a brawl at a barber shop!
What are you doing with that sword?
Huh?
Hand this weapon over immediately!
Hey, stop it, would ya?
Don't pull it out!
Polnareff!
Oh, damn it.
His eyes.
That stare.
Polnareff is being controlled
by the sword's spell.
Hey! You there!
You drew the sword!
I drew the sword, did I?
Officer, you should really be more
careful with your accusations.
since you call yourself
a servant of the law.
Take it easy! What are you doing?
I'm simply attacking the culprit
who uncheateth the sword!
I don't know who you are
or where you're hiding,
but I think it's safe to say
Polnareff is under your control.
Come to think of it, I've never had
to fight against Polnareff before.
And I can't pull punches
with Chariot as an opponent.
If I'm not smart about this...
I could end up killing Polnareff.
As I said before,
at this point I've already witnessed Star
Platinum's entire repertoire of moves.
And if I've done battle with you once
before, then I will never lose again!
Okay, now.
His speed...
It's incredible!
He's getting fast enough to outpace me!
I have to find a way to stop that sword!
I'll catch it again!
He's sped up!
This time, I'll take your hand!
This speed and power are overwhelming.
Without a doubt, this is the
fastest stand I've ever faced.
At the rate I'm going,
this won't end well.
I have to fight Polnareff with
everything I've got, or I'm dead.
So, you headbutted the sword after you
realized you couldn't catch my blade.
Honestly I didn't think you were capable
of something like that I almost had you!
But now I've acquired that
skill as well Jotaro I can tell
that you're thinking The only
way to survive is to kill
your friend Polnareff even if
you wanted to It's naive to
think it'd be that easy take
a close look Jotaro what am I?
about to show you will put an
end to this once and for all.
So let's see if you can beat this, Totoro!
Feast your eyes on the
Silver Chariot and Anubis!
Two-Sword Technique!
Damn it.
This extra sword, coupled
with this accelerating speed,
even Star Platinum won't last long.
What's the matter?
Are you feeling a little tired, Jojaro?
No!
I'll stop him before he kills me.
Starfinger!
My right arm is as light as a feather now.
Interesting, I guess that was an option.
Didn't see that coming, did you?
Round two, armor release!
You fool,
your ridiculous aura aura is no match for
two swords wielded by
two master swordsmen.
Your stomach is wide open!
I've got you now!
I did it! I win!
Master Dio, I've exterminated Jotaro!
I, Anubis, have finally put him down!
Victory is mine!
Just forget it!
You're not going to be able
to pull out that blade!
Give up already!
I'm not sure your tiny brain has realized
it, but I've surpassed Star Platinum!
And now, the final thrust!
The...
final thrust?
Yes, precisely!
Once I slice open your bowels,
Master Dio will rejoice!
Please, stop this.
Don't drive the blade any further.
It...
it'll be murder.
Nice try!
But you won't get any mercy from me!
I can't wait to spill your guts!
What the devil?!
You're breaking me!
I have to fall free!
No! Stop!
Maybe I'm wrong, but weren't you
saying something about slicing me open?
I told you it'd be murder.
But the murder I was talking
about was yours, friend.
You're a pretty easy target when
the sword isn't moving around.
Dammit, what a pain in the ass.
This was the toughest opponent I've faced.
At last, the attack took everything
I had in me and then some.
Luckily,
it was just enough to
defeat him before he could
learn it like he did
the rest of our attacks.
This is new.
I've never been so exhausted.
I have to find Avdol and the old man.
What in the world just happened?
The sword didn't possess me like
it did all the other guys, did it?
Yeah, it did.
But it's over now. Forgive me.
Just get the old man and Avdol.
I'm too tired to walk.
Huh?
Wow, it's so shiny.
Now, I've learned that trick.
My original stand user was the
swordsmith who forged me 500 years ago.
He may have perished centuries ago, but
I survive as a stand with no master.
Master Tio liberated me from the
gloomy shadows of a dusty museum.
And speaking of Master Tio, his stand,
the world, is far more powerful than I.
That's why I pledged my undying loyalty.
Jotaro, I swear on my
life, I will murder you!
I know your strength, your speed.
You won't see it coming until
it's too late to stop it!
I'll stab you in the back!
Now die, Jotaro!
What just happened?
Son of a... I missed!
I was tripped by a dog!
Where the hell did that mutt come from?
Hey, Iggy, what are you eating?
Wait a second.
Is that a nasty old sucker?
Eating right off the ground
again, you filthy mutt.
You've got to be kidding!
It's the Nile River!
No, this can't be happening!
What did I do to deserve this cruel fate?
If I fall into the river I'm
done for, I'll rust away!
Somebody stop me!
I'm heading for a wall!
The wall will stop me!
Lucky me!
What the? Shit!
I was so panicked about
falling into the water
that I accidentally face
right through the wall!
I'm gonna fall in!
Yes, it's a ship!
I'm saved.
If I wedge into those planks!
That guy's curiosity will
make him pull me out.
And then I'll take over his pathetic mind.
Once I'm safely back on dry land!
I'll use his body to
take revenge on Jotaro.
What?
A cow's on board Stop thrashing around.
Hey, calm down!
Would you call it, you stupid cow?
I know!
I'll take over the cow's mind!
Then it'll be a cinch...
I'm gonna go to make it inside!
Hey, over there.
That cow's really rocking
the boat, don't you think?
Oh, good grief.
Who gives a damn?
Just go get the old man an Avdol, will ya?
HELP MEEEEEEEE!
Hey! You! Oh, fishies! Look down here!
Come on!
Swim over to me!
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?
Hey, Mr. Crab!
It's a pleasure to meet ya!
Would you mind doing me a
favor and taking me ashore?
I'll give you something yummy
Wait, Mr.
Crab, you just can't leave me here I'll
be rushing through in a couple of days.
Please help me!
Don't leave me here.
Oh, I'm so alone?
Stupid mutt.
What are you staring at?
There's nothing to eat
over there, Fleabag.
Why, you stinkin' little...
Aw, man!
What the hell have you been eating?
Come on, Polareff.
To think, all of that happened without us.
You fought the Anubis stan, huh?
That must have been rough, Jotaro.
Yeah, it was.
That's the last time I
ever go anywhere with him.
Stop it already, you stupid mutt!
Get the hell off my face!
The average tourist to Egypt is mostly
unaware of the country's
rich ethnic diversity.
For example, take this Egyptian man
wearing the traditional Jalabiya.
Or this Egyptian Nubian.
And here is a Bedouin from
Egypt's desert region.
This gentleman hails from India.
And as a random example, here's
another Egyptian citizen.
Hey, that fox has got some smoking
hot legs that are out of this world.
I can't keep my eyes off her.
Wow, those puppies will
pull you right in, you know.
Thank you.
Hey, Mr.
Joestar, is something wrong?
I was right!
What the hell do you think
you're doing, you old pervert?
Something's wrong here!
Now, how did that old saying go again?
Yeah!
My body's turned into a magnet!
Curiosity killed that cat.
I'm gonna die!